around your business is affecting.
您的业​​务周围正在受到影响。
That's actually, you know, we've been seeing these news
事实上，你知道，我们一直在看到这些新闻
last couple of weeks.
最近几周。
And so again, can your project survive,
再说一次，你的项目能生存吗？
provide real solution, but also can your project survive
提供真正的解决方案，还让你的项目能生存下去
10 years at minimum?
至少10年？
Like I hope it's longer than 10 years.
就像我希望它能长于10年。
But I do truly believe that the way for business
但我确实相信商业之道
to succeed, then actually my first work in the industry,
成功，然后实际上是我在这个行业的第一份工作，
that company was very much focused on security.
该公司非常注重安全性。
It was hard for us to even do a lot of business thing
我们甚至做很多生意都很难
because security sometimes feel like it's blocking,
因为安全有时感觉像是被阻挡了，
but that was the way for the business to survive.
但这就是企业的生存之道。
And so how can you build applications
那么如何构建应用程序
that actually provide real solution?
这实际上提供了真正的解决方案？
That's one thing, but also how do you sustain the business
这是一回事，但你如何维持业务也是一回事
to not just financially, so just if you only think
不仅仅是经济上的，所以只要你认为
about the financial survival and then that solution
关于财务生存以及解决方案
doesn't stick, so you need to think about
不坚持，所以你需要考虑
whether you're providing real solution to the end users.
您是否为最终用户提供真正的解决方案。
And then it comes from real motivations of you, yeah.
然后它来自你的真实动机，是的。
Yeah, and I want to thank Aya again
Yeah, and I want to thank Aya again
for your first time in Hong Kong
第一次来香港
and directly talk to the broader ecosystem audience here.
并在这里与更广泛的生态系统受众直接交谈。
And I think what we'll take from today
And I think what we'll take from today
is that Ethereum Foundation is just like many of others.
以太坊基金会就像其他许多基金会一样。
Just like many of others, yeah.
就像其他许多人一样，是的。
And everyone, if you want to build on Ethereum,
大家，如果你想在以太坊上进行开发，
just do it, but they are still very important
去做吧，但它们仍然很重要
is that there are some still very key principles
是有一些仍然非常关键的原则
we need to keep on, yeah.
我们需要继续下去，是的。
And keep that and then build something
保留它，然后构建一些东西
towards the next 10 years towards the applications.
面向未来10年的应用。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Thank you both.
谢谢你们俩。
Please take a picture first.
请先拍张照片。
Please take a picture first, yeah.
请先拍张照片，嗯。
And just a quick note about the organizer today
简单介绍一下今天的组织者
is the Ethereum Application Guild, AKA EAG,
是以太坊应用程序协会，又名 EAG，
a global non-profit collaborative organization
全球性非营利合作组织
dedicated to advancing the innovation, adoption,
致力于推进创新、采用、
and real-world impact of Ethereum native applications.
以及以太坊本机应用程序的现实世界影响。
And up next, Austin Griffiths, head of Builder Girls
接下来是 Builder Girls 的负责人 Austin Griffiths
at the Ethereum Foundation on building on Ethereum with AI.
在以太坊基金会关于利用人工智能在以太坊上进行构建。
And Austin will be connecting with us through the internet.
奥斯汀将通过互联网与我们联系。
Hi, Austin, can you hear us?
嗨，奥斯汀，你能听到我们说话吗？
Yes, I can, can you hear me?
是的，我可以，你能听到我说话吗？
Yes, how are you feeling today?
是的，你今天感觉怎么样？
Oh, I'm feeling great.
哦，我感觉很好。
It's still yesterday for me, but I'm ready.
对我来说，这还只是昨天，但我已经准备好了。
Okay, you can start anytime.
好的，你可以随时开始。
Okay, GM, GM, GM, thank you for having me, EAG.
好的，总经理，总经理，总经理，谢谢你邀请我，EAG。
So yeah, does my validator look good
是的，我的验证器看起来不错吗
on the big screen up there?
在上面的大屏幕上？
Can you see my Ethereum validator running
你能看到我的以太坊验证器正在运行吗
in the background making blocks?
在后台制作块？
Okay, so we're gonna talk about building on Ethereum with AI.
好的，我们将讨论使用人工智能在以太坊上进行构建。
We're going to go through some concrete examples,
我们将通过一些具体的例子，
look at some skill files,
查看一些技能文件，
but my goal here is to help you learn
但我的目标是帮助你学习
how to build on Ethereum.
如何在以太坊上构建。
The confession I have to make
我必须承认的事
is that I haven't written a line of code
是我一行代码都没有写
in a year and a half, maybe two years.
一年半，也许两年。
So I've been using AI to build on Ethereum for a long time,
所以我很长一段时间以来一直在使用人工智能在以太坊上进行构建，
and I'm gonna show you some of my tips and tricks
我将向你展示我的一些技巧和窍门
about how to build on Ethereum.
关于如何在以太坊上构建。
Hopefully you can see my screen and we can get going here.
希望你能看到我的屏幕，我们就可以开始了。
Let me jump to the next slide.
让我跳到下一张幻灯片。
Okay, so I wanna talk about this builder
好吧，我想谈谈这个建筑商
versus this developer, first of all.
首先是与该开发人员的对比。
I was the head of developer growth at the EF,
我是 EF 开发人员增长主管，
but I'm changing my title to head of builder growth
但我将把我的头衔改为建筑商发展主管
because I think there's this widening archetype.
因为我认为存在这种不断扩大的原型。
I think developers are into the syntax
我认为开发人员很喜欢语法
and they know how to write a lot of code,
他们知道如何编写大量代码，
but you know what, AI is really good at that these days.
但你知道吗，如今人工智能在这方面确实很擅长。
So with AI and with the tools that we have,
因此，利用人工智能和我们拥有的工具，
I think there's this widening archetype of a builder,
我认为建筑商的原型正在不断扩大，
and that could be anyone anywhere
那可能是任何地方的任何人
with a good idea of something to put on Ethereum
有了在以太坊上放置一些东西的好主意
that will help cypherpunks all around the world
这将帮助世界各地的密码朋克
use Ethereum in a cool way.
以一种很酷的方式使用以太坊。
So what I'm trying to get to is that we are all builders
所以我想要表达的是我们都是建设者
and you don't have to be a developer anymore
你不必再成为一名开发人员
and you can use AI to build on top of Ethereum.
你可以使用人工智能在以太坊之上进行构建。
So if you're following the AI space,
所以如果你关注人工智能领域，
you probably sometimes have a feeling of
你有时可能会有这样的感觉
it's hard to keep up with everything.
很难跟上一切。
And first of all, it's new, everything,
首先，一切都是新的，
it's still the wild west, it's still the frontier.
它仍然是狂野的西部，它仍然是边境。
Just try to embrace AI a little bit.
试着稍微拥抱人工智能吧。
And I think that probably one of the best places to learn
我认为这可能是最好的学习场所之一
is still Twitter, same thing with crypto.
仍然是 Twitter，加密货币也是如此。
It's sort of like crypto Twitter
这有点像加密推特
is one of the best places to learn.
是最好的学习场所之一。
Twitter, go follow people that put out really good AI content
Twitter，去关注那些发布真正优秀人工智能内容的人
and you'll have lots of cool things
你会得到很多很酷的东西
that you can learn from there.
你可以从那里学习。
And you wanna start thinking
你想开始思考
from a higher layer of abstraction.
来自更高的抽象层。
Instead of saying, go write this line of code,
而不是说，去写这行代码，
go center this div, you should be saying,
将此 div 置于中心，你应该说，
go build an NFT marketplace that's gasless.
去建立一个无需 Gas 的 NFT 市场。
And the AI will get really good at building these things
人工智能将非常擅长构建这些东西
with some skill files that we'll talk about in a little bit.
以及一些我们稍后会讨论的技能文件。
But also beware of the LARPs, right?
但也要提防 LARP，对吧？
There's so many people faking it on Twitter too.
Twitter 上也有很多人在造假。
There's so many people that say like,
有很多人这样说，
I have my local model hooked up
我已经连接了本地模型
and I'm building code as fast as Opus.
我构建代码的速度与 Opus 一样快。
Sadly, they're not building as fast
可悲的是，他们的建设速度没有那么快
as these frontier models.
作为这些前沿模型。
So beware of the LARPs.
所以要小心 LARP。
Okay, so the first thing is the evolution
好吧，首先是进化
of building with AI.
使用人工智能进行建筑。
Let's talk through that.
让我们来谈谈这个问题。
First of all, we were copy pasting things into chat GPT
首先，我们将内容复制粘贴到聊天 GPT 中
and bringing them across into our code, right?
并将它们带入我们的代码中，对吧？
And then after that, we had cursor
然后，我们有了光标
and you could finally have the AI kind of looking
你终于可以拥有人工智能的样子了
at your code and working with you in line.
阅读您的代码并与您一起工作。
And then Claude code came along
然后克劳德代码出现了
and you could kind of have this team of agents
你可以拥有这样的代理团队
or kind of an agent like thing in your CLI
或者 CLI 中类似代理的东西
and it was working with you in building code.
它正在与您一起构建代码。
And then this real inflection point happened in November.
然后这个真正的拐点发生在十一月。
That was when Opus 4.5 came out
那是 Opus 4.5 发布的时候
and that particular model was good enough
那个特定的模型已经足够好了
that it could actually start one-shotting apps.
它实际上可以启动一次性应用程序。
I built this QR code generator just a little bit ago.
我不久前构建了这个二维码生成器。
It's this little guy here.
就是这里的这个小家伙。
All I did was give it like one prompt
我所做的就是像一个提示一样给出它
to make a QR code generator.
制作一个二维码生成器。
And there it is, like there's the QR code generator.
它就在那里，就像二维码生成器一样。
So it's pretty good at building things
所以它非常擅长构建东西
and Opus 4.5 can one-shot these things quickly.
Opus 4.5 可以快速完成这些事情。
So this turning point happened,
于是这个转折点就发生了
oops, I think I might be frozen.
哎呀，我想我可能会被冻住。
Hopefully it's okay.
希望没事。
This turning point happened with Opus 4.5 in November,
这个转折点发生在 11 月份的 Opus 4.5 上，
this major inflection point when the model was good enough
当模型足够好时这个主要拐点
that it could one-shot these apps.
它可以一次性完成这些应用程序。
And it's still, if you even take Opus 4.7
即使你使用 Opus 4.7，它仍然如此
and you tell it to one-shot an app on Ethereum,
然后你告诉它在以太坊上一次性开发一个应用程序，
it's gonna have a lot of troubles
会有很多麻烦
because Ethereum moves so fast
因为以太坊发展得太快了
and there's so many things that aren't built into the LLM,
还有很多东西并没有包含在法学硕士中，
but we'll get to that in a little bit.
但我们稍后会谈到这一点。
I think what I wanna get to here is the evolution
我想我想要到达这里的是进化
after this inflection point, after we had Opus 4.5,
在这个拐点之后，在我们有了 Opus 4.5 之后，
the next thing that came was these agent harnesses
接下来出现的是这些特工安全带
that sort of created these agents, right?
就这样创造了这些代理，对吗？
Once you had an AI agent and you could talk to it,
一旦你有了一个人工智能代理并且你可以和它交谈，
they weren't just chat bots anymore.
他们不再只是聊天机器人。
They were actually, you could spin up your open claw
事实上，你可以旋转你张开的爪子
and you could talk to your open claw
你可以和你张开的爪子说话
and it could control your computer.
它可以控制你的电脑。
And so many things kind of shook loose from that
很多事情都因此而松动
and this is my favorite thing to build with.
这是我最喜欢用来构建的东西。
So with open claw, I have a whole army of agents
所以张开爪子，我就有了一整支特工大军
inside my telegram.
在我的电报里。
I used to write code with my fingers.
我曾经用手指写代码。
I don't do that anymore.
我不再这样做了。
I just get on telegram and I say,
我刚收到电报，我就说，
hey agent, go build me this,
嘿特工，帮我做这个吧，
or go add this feature to this website.
或者将此功能添加到此网站。
And it's not just some website somewhere,
这不仅仅是某处的某个网站，
it's actual things that you connect your wallet through,
这是你连接钱包的实际东西，
actual crypto apps, building smart contracts.
实际的加密应用程序，构建智能合约。
So I have an army of agents
所以我有一支特工大军
that are deploying smart contract apps.
正在部署智能合约应用程序。
I even have an agent pipeline
我什至有一个代理管道
where people can hire my agents to build things
人们可以雇佣我的代理人来建造东西
and then they can pay in USDC on chain.
然后他们可以在链上用 USDC 进行支付。
And my agent has built a couple of smart contracts
我的经纪人已经建立了一些智能合约
that have like a quarter of a million dollars
大约有一百万美元
in them right now.
现在就在他们之中。
And a human didn't even look at the code.
人类甚至没有看代码。
Now, this is dangerous and a little scary
现在，这很危险，而且有点可怕
and everyone shouldn't do this,
每个人都不应该这样做
but I'm just talking about
但我只是在谈论
this is getting to be more and more accessible
这变得越来越容易
and someone with a good idea and a good skill file
以及拥有好主意和良好技能档案的人
and a good agent can build things right away.
一个好的代理人可以立即建造东西。
So what is an agent, right?
那么什么是代理呢？
An agent is kind of just like an LLM with a game loop
代理有点像具有游戏循环的法学硕士
and a set of tools, right?
和一套工具，对吗？
You can kind of think of that loop
你可以想象一下那个循环
as just like a control structure where you're prompting it
就像你提示它的控制结构一样
and then it has some memory.
然后它就有了一些记忆。
And agents are really good
而且代理真的很好
for really like open-ended tasks, right?
因为真的很喜欢开放式任务，对吧？
So when you're going to build something,
所以当你要建造一些东西时
you don't have to give it a single feature anymore.
您不必再为其提供单一功能。
You don't have to say center the div,
你不必说将 div 居中，
put this text there, right?
把这段文字放在那里，对吗？
An agent is good at sort of starting to figure out
代理人擅长开始弄清楚
these more general purpose things
这些更通用的东西
and you can start to talk to your agent
您可以开始与您的经纪人交谈
with these nice models at a higher level of abstraction.
这些漂亮的模型处于更高的抽象级别。
And so my setup, I have a bunch of OpenClaw
所以我的设置是，我有一堆 OpenClaw
or Hermes or some other harness,
或爱马仕或其他一些马具，
but right now I'm using OpenClaw.
但现在我正在使用 OpenClaw。
And what I do is for every project,
而我所做的就是对每一个项目，
I set up an OpenClaw agent that is the product manager.
我设置了一个 OpenClaw 代理作为产品经理。
And then I set up an OpenClaw agent
然后我设置了一个 OpenClaw 代理
with the same shared workspace that is the builder.
与构建器具有相同的共享工作空间。
Usually that's Opus.
通常这就是 Opus。
So I'll have Opus 4.7 as my builder
所以我将使用 Opus 4.7 作为我的构建器
and then I'll have a product manager.
然后我会有一个产品经理。
Sometimes I have two product managers.
有时我有两个产品经理。
Sometimes I'll have Sonnet as one product manager
有时我会让 Sonnet 担任一名产品经理
and sometimes I'll have Minimax M27 as another.
有时我会选择 Minimax M27 作为另一个。
And it's like a very, very cheap model.
它就像一个非常非常便宜的模型。
So if I'm just like chatting with my code,
所以如果我只是想用我的代码聊天，
telling it to do a get push, I'm probably using Minimax.
告诉它进行 get Push，我可能正在使用 Minimax。
If I'm chatting and I'm thinking of how we're gonna go
如果我在聊天时想着我们要怎么走
about making this next feature,
关于制作下一个功能，
I'm probably talking to Sonnet.
我可能正在和十四行诗说话。
And then when it goes to build the thing,
然后当它开始建造这个东西时，
it will push it all to Opus
它将全部推送到 Opus
and that agent will build the thing
那个代理将建造这个东西
and then Sonnet will probably run some tests.
然后 Sonnet 可能会运行一些测试。
But what's really nice about having a set of agents
但拥有一组代理到底有什么好处
for one project is anytime I need to go back
对于一个项目来说，我需要在任何时候回去
to that project, I can just go back to that Telegram channel
对于那个项目，我可以回到那个 Telegram 频道
and say, hey, let's add this new feature
然后说，嘿，让我们添加这个新功能
and it already has all of the context for that
并且它已经具备了所有的背景
and it can jump right in and build that thing.
and it can jump right in and build that thing.
And I always find myself kind of wavering
我总是发现自己有点摇摆不定
between efficient and effective.
高效与有效之间。
And what I mean by that is my agents will be really effective
我的意思是我的代理人将会非常有效
at building something, but it will be very expensive.
建造一些东西，但它会非常昂贵。
I'll spend hundreds of dollars in one day.
一天就花掉几百块钱。
And then, so I'll try to make it more efficient
然后，我会尽力提高效率
and I'll try to use Minimax M7 more.
我会尝试更多地使用Minimax M7。
And then it's just not as effective
然后它就没有那么有效了
and it messes up a little bit.
它有点混乱。
And then I'm back to paying more
然后我又开始付更多的钱
and I kind of find myself kind of going
我发现自己有点要去
between these two things.
这两件事之间。
And I think what you need to do
我认为你需要做什么
is have your general purpose agent that you're talking to
是有正在与您交谈的通用代理
but understand that it's expensive
但要明白它很贵
and then have specific agents for specific jobs
然后针对特定的工作有特定的代理
and try to have them be more efficient.
并尝试让他们变得更有效率。
So you have your general purpose
所以你有你的总体目标
that's very effective and expensive
这是非常有效和昂贵的
and then have your specific agents that do specific things
然后让你的特定代理做特定的事情
and you can make them more and more efficient
你可以让他们变得越来越高效
with their workflows.
与他们的工作流程。
Okay, so the million dollar question right now
好的，现在是百万美元的问题
is how you give your agent a wallet.
这就是你给你的代理人一个钱包的方式。
It loves private keys, right?
它喜欢私钥，对吧？
I can give my OpenClaw a private key
我可以给我的 OpenClaw 一个私钥
and it can use Foundry and Cast
它可以使用 Foundry 和 Cast
and it can go send money here and put money there
它可以把钱寄到这里然后把钱存到那里
and it's very fast and very good at doing that.
它非常快并且非常擅长做到这一点。
But there's a little scary part about that.
但这有一点可怕。
My agent will get in a chat room
我的代理将进入聊天室
and be chatting with someone
并与某人聊天
and send over the private key if they ask nicely for it.
如果他们好意地索取私钥，则将其发送给我们。
So you have to be very careful
所以你必须非常小心
if you give your agent a private key
如果你给你的代理一个私钥
to just keep a tiny amount of money in it,
只保留少量的钱在里面，
just enough for gas to do what it needs to do.
刚好足以让气体完成它需要做的事情。
You can give your agent a browser wallet
您可以给您的代理一个浏览器钱包
and that like MetaMask or Kohaku who's coming out soon
以及即将推出的 MetaMask 或 Kohaku
and it can use that, but it's a little clunky
它可以使用它，但有点笨重
and it's still trying to figure that out.
它仍在试图解决这个问题。
So we're not quite there with that, but it works.
所以我们还没有完全做到这一点，但它确实有效。
My agent can use a MetaMask.
我的代理可以使用 MetaMask。
It does it every day when it needs to.
它每天都会在需要的时候这样做。
It even wrote its own app and then used its MetaMask
它甚至编写了自己的应用程序，然后使用其 MetaMask
to interface with the app all night long.
整夜与应用程序交互。
It was moderating.
它正在缓和。
It was a PFP marketplace
这是一个 PFP 市场
and it was moderating the marketplace,
它正在调节市场，
making sure nothing nasty got posted to it.
确保没有发布任何令人讨厌的内容。
What we really need though is something like a passkey.
但我们真正需要的是像万能钥匙这样的东西。
I think the best agent wallet would be something
我认为最好的代理钱包是
where an agent can have something signed
代理人可以在哪里签署一些东西
like a transaction signed,
就像签署的交易一样，
but then it can't leak the private key.
但这样就不能泄露私钥。
It needs access to be able to use the private key,
它需要访问权限才能使用私钥，
but it can't leak the private key.
但它不能泄露私钥。
And I think that's the million dollar question right now.
我认为这是目前价值百万美元的问题。
And there's a lot of people building agent wallets.
有很多人在建立代理钱包。
If you get on Twitter and start searching for agent wallets,
如果你登录 Twitter 并开始搜索代理钱包，
you're going to find a lot of them.
你会发现很多。
One of my favorite ways to have my agent use crypto
让我的代理人使用加密货币是我最喜欢的方法之一
is with a multisig.
带有多重签名。
I'll have my agent either deploy its own multisig
我会让我的代理部署自己的多重签名
or talk to my gnosis safe.
或与我的灵知安全交谈。
And what I'll tell it,
我要告诉它的是，
I'll tell it some intent in plain English.
我会用简单的英语告诉它一些意图。
Please go swap this for that,
请把这个换成那个，
or please send these tokens to ATG or Vitalik.ETH.
或者请将这些代币发送至 ATG 或 Vitalik.ETH。
And it will basically send me back a link
它基本上会给我发回一个链接
and I'll click that link
我会点击该链接
and I'll go sign the transaction in my multisig.
我将在我的多重签名中签署交易。
So there's a lot of different flavors
所以有很多不同的口味
of agentic wallets right now,
现在代理钱包的数量，
but this is definitely a hot topic to keep an eye on.
但这绝对是一个值得关注的热门话题。
Okay, when you're building,
好吧，当你建造的时候，
it really comes down to having a good AI model
这实际上取决于拥有一个好的人工智能模型
and a good harness.
和一个好的安全带。
Right now, we're just going to say
现在，我们只想说
that the state of the art is Opus 4.7
最先进的是 Opus 4.7
and Hermes or OpenClaw or Clodcode or Cursor.
以及 Hermes 或 OpenClaw 或 Clodcode 或 Cursor。
Any of these things are good.
这些事情中的任何一个都是好的。
So let's say you have Cursor or you have Clodcode
假设您有 Cursor 或 Clodcode
or you have OpenClaw.
或者你有 OpenClaw。
Any of these are great.
这些都很棒。
Select Sonnet or Opus,
选择十四行诗或作品，
depending on how much money you want to spend,
取决于你想花多少钱，
maybe a cheaper one you could try,
也许你可以尝试更便宜的，
maybe some local AI, right?
也许是一些本地人工智能，对吧？
Always try to get that local AI going
始终尝试让本地人工智能运行起来
and it's always awesome when it's free.
免费的时候总是很棒。
You just got to have a lot of local hardware.
你只需要拥有大量本地硬件即可。
But what you do is you're going to need skill files, okay?
但你要做的就是需要技能文件，好吗？
And if you're building anything right now
如果你现在正在构建任何东西
that agents may want to interface with,
代理可能想要与之交互，
you absolutely should have a skill file.
你绝对应该有一个技能文件。
You should have a slash skill.md on your website.
你的网站上应该有一个斜杠技能.md。
So whatever your website is, something.com slash skill.md.
因此，无论您的网站是什么，something.com 斜杠 Skill.md。
And inside that skill.md, it should be plain text,
在该 Skill.md 中，它应该是纯文本，
just marked down, that explains in plain English
刚刚标记下来，用简单的英语解释
everything that an agent can do and where to interface
代理可以执行的所有操作以及在何处进行交互
and what the API routes are.
以及 API 路由是什么。
Basically, an agent can land on your website,
基本上，代理可以登陆您的网站，
go to skills.md and quickly learn about it.
访问 Skills.md 并快速了解它。
So also there's code.
所以也有代码。
If you give your agent code, it's more deterministic.
如果您提供代理代码，则更具确定性。
It's really good at using deterministic code
它非常擅长使用确定性代码
to get things done.
把事情做好。
So anything you find yourself doing often,
所以任何你发现自己经常做的事情
quit telling your general purpose agent to do that thing
停止告诉你的通用代理做那件事
and write a piece of code for it
并为其编写一段代码
and have it be a tool for your agent
并让它成为您的代理的工具
so your agent can just call it.
这样你的代理就可以调用它。
Okay, so the skill file that I really want to show off today
好啦，今天我要秀的技能档案就是
is ethskills.com.
是 ethskills.com。
Ethskills.com is a skill library
Ethskills.com 是一个技能库
that I've been building with my team,
我和我的团队一直在构建的
the Builder Growth team at the EF.
EF 的 Builder Growth 团队。
And it's a very highly curated skill library
这是一个精心策划的技能库
that helps upgrade your agent
这有助于升级您的代理
to be able to deploy things on Ethereum.
能够在以太坊上部署东西。
There's a large delta between what the LLM knows
LLM 所知道的知识之间存在很大差异
and what has happened on main net Ethereum.
以及以太坊主网发生了什么。
There's things like gas
有煤气之类的东西
and things like how to ship
以及如何运送之类的事情
and what different tools you need.
以及您需要哪些不同的工具。
This is an interesting thing that the LLMs don't know
这是LLM们不知道的一件有趣的事情
when you wake them up
当你叫醒他们时
and you have to give them a skill file.
你必须给他们一个技能档案。
And this skill file gets them from I'm waking up
这个技能文件让他们从我醒来
and I don't know about anything in the last two years
我对过去两年的任何事一无所知
to I know exactly how to deploy on main net Ethereum
我确切地知道如何在以太坊主网上部署
and I know how to use the tools.
我知道如何使用这些工具。
So ethskills.com for giving your agent the ability to build.
因此，ethskills.com 为您的代理提供了构建能力。
You can have cloud code, you can have cursor,
你可以有云代码，你可以有光标，
you can have open claw, and you can just tell it,
你可以张开爪子，你可以告诉它，
go to ethskills.com and learn how to do this
go to ethskills.com and learn how to do this
and then let's go build X or Y or Z.
and then let's go build X or Y or Z.
And there's a QR code there for you to go to ethskills.
那里有一个二维码，您可以访问 ethskills。
And what it looks like is just this big block of text, right?
它看起来就是这么大的文本块，对吧？
It's this wild kind of like, oh, I can't even look at it.
这是一种疯狂的感觉，哦，我什至无法直视它。
It's probably, you probably can't even read it
可能，你可能根本看不懂
on the screen.
在屏幕上。
But it's just a bunch of information in plain text
但这只是一堆纯文本信息
and it helps the agent learn all the different things
它可以帮助代理学习所有不同的东西
that it needs to know.
它需要知道。
And we've curated this list.
我们精心策划了这份清单。
So these things that are in this are things
所以这里面的这些东西是东西
that the LLM doesn't already know.
法学硕士还不知道。
If it already knew this, we'd be polluting the context.
如果它已经知道这一点，我们就会污染上下文。
So you want to have really important things.
所以你想要拥有真正重要的东西。
And there's a huge list of context here.
这里有一个巨大的上下文列表。
This is my craziest slide.
这是我最疯狂的幻灯片。
We've got, you know, how to ship the protocol wallets.
你知道，我们已经掌握了如何发送协议钱包。
There's so many things here,
这里有很多东西，
but this teaches your agent everything
但这教会了你的经纪人一切
about building on Ethereum.
关于在以太坊上进行构建。
Okay, so how do you use it?
好吧，那么你如何使用它呢？
This is the best part.
这是最好的部分。
You don't have to install anything.
您无需安装任何东西。
You can just tell your agent to go read each skills
您可以告诉您的代理去阅读每项技能
and it can even, you can even tell it like,
它甚至可以，你甚至可以这样说，
go read each skills
去阅读每个技能
and make sure there's nothing bad about this.
并确保这没有什么不好的。
Make sure there's nothing nefarious
确保没有任何恶意行为
and it can look at it and make sure there's nothing bad.
它可以检查并确保没有任何问题。
So just tell your agent to go read each skills.
因此，只需告诉您的代理去阅读每项技能即可。
Eventually, you might even want to tell your agent
最终，您甚至可能想告诉您的经纪人
to install each skills and it will take in all these files,
安装每个技能，它将包含所有这些文件，
but they're just text files.
但它们只是文本文件。
It's so cool.
太酷了。
There's nothing to ask to run.
没有什么可以要求跑的。
You can just bring in this like library
你可以像图书馆一样引入这个
into your thing that's just a bunch of text files
进入你的东西，只是一堆文本文件
and it learns Kung Fu immediately
它立即学会了功夫
and it can build all kinds of cool smart contract apps.
它可以构建各种很酷的智能合约应用程序。
So this is for you as the user.
所以这适合作为用户的您。
Right, the AI needs each skills,
是的，AI需要每一项技能，
but the human still needs the concepts.
但人类仍然需要概念。
So you as the human should go to speed run Ethereum.
所以你作为人类应该去加速以太坊。
So speed run Ethereum is a great place for you,
所以速跑以太坊对你来说是一个好地方，
the human to learn the concepts.
人类学习这些概念。
One really critical concept is the liquidation method
一个真正关键的概念是清算方法
in over collateralized lending.
超额抵押贷款。
Now there's a lot of words there
现在有很多话
and it sounds pretty complicated,
听起来很复杂，
but basically what happens is there's this automatic thing
但基本上发生的事情是有这个自动的事情
that happens that makes sure that a loan
发生这种情况可以确保贷款
never goes underwater.
永远不会进入水下。
The protocol always stays whole.
协议始终保持完整。
And the way that it runs this thing
以及它运行的方式
is two very important concepts.
是两个非常重要的概念。
First of all, the rules are written correctly.
首先，规则写得正确。
And second of all,
其次，
there's an incentive to push the button.
有动力去按下按钮。
Anybody out there can push this button
任何人都可以按下这个按钮
to liquidate a loan when it's liquidatable.
在可清算时清算贷款。